<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on DevBlog - Jacob Timmerman</title>
    <link>https://example.org/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on DevBlog - Jacob Timmerman</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 20:28:38 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://example.org/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>FourthDevBlogChipotle</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/fourthdevblogchipotle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 20:28:38 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/fourthdevblogchipotle/</guid>
      <description>Chipotle Social Media Site Tough tough day today. I started the day by formatting the basic layout of the modal for the review page. This included sections for ratings 0-5 stars on food quality, quantity, staff quality, additional notes, and time taken to recieve food. This part went quite well and I was able to get example submissions working as well as resetting the values of the submission after closing/submitting a forum.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ThirdDevBlogChipotle</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/thirddevblogchipotle/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 21:53:07 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/thirddevblogchipotle/</guid>
      <description>Chipotle Social Media Site Soooooo, I got side tracked a bit today. I noticed that for some of locations the address and name matched exactly. So, I did some digging and found that there are cross streets listed for each location that I could use as a stand-in for the name. However, I soon found out, that not all of the locations had these cross streets. I then thought &amp;ldquo;well, if there is only one Chipotle in a given city, then I can just use the city name as the name of the Chipotle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SecondDevBlogChipotle</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/seconddevblogchipotle/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 21:24:58 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/seconddevblogchipotle/</guid>
      <description>Chipotle Social Media Site As I mentioned at the tail end of yesterdays blog, today was mainly to start work on moving the data to a database and figure out the API stuff&#xA;However, when I started working today I found that I could just use Node.js to create the API server, and use a library to port the csv into json that could be used by the Javascript in index.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FirstDevBlogChipotle</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/firstdevblogchipotle/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 12:27:02 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/firstdevblogchipotle/</guid>
      <description>Chipotle Social Media Site Did some preliminary research yesterday and found that something very similar to what I want to do has already been done. The site has a map as the default background with pins for locations of Chipotle&amp;rsquo;s that you can click and see the rating and other information for.&#xA;I would like to do something similar to this, but instead of just ratings and a few comments, I want to have a live feed, similar to Instagram, where you can see pictures and ratings of food that was just prepared at the location!</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
